bitwords.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy Bitwords Media NYC

  * 1\.  Our Commitment To Privacy
  * 2\.  The Information We Collect
  * 3\.  How We Use Information
  * 4\.  Our Commitment To Data Security
  * 5\.  Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
  * 6\.  How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  * 7\.  How To Contact Us

##  Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## The Information We Collect: 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Bitwords Media website (www.bitwords.com). On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name 
  * Email address
  * Phone number 
  * Required Services
  * Project Description 
  * Estimated Budget
  * Plan to Start Your Project
  * (etc.) 

## The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself sending us request for online service quote for web design, web development & internet marketing services or contacting us for any other information through contact us page or call back page to provide us your name, phone number and reason of contact. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to discuss more about your project.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our services catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy: 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by email us at info@bitwords.com. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 800 223 1891 or send us an email at info@bitwords.com.
